[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Well, it was getting dark and I was worn out from the stress of the day, so I decided to get ready for bed. Sadly, this prompted a panic attack due to my ablutophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Bathing", "incorrect_answers": ["Going to sleep", "The dark", "Pajamas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is thought that Triceratops was able to run how fast?", "correct_answer": "15 mph", "incorrect_answers": ["40 mph", "20 mph", "30 mph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played the part of Samanthas dad Jim Baker in Sixteen Candles?", "correct_answer": "Paul Dooley", "incorrect_answers": ["Moses Gunn", "Paul Schmooley", "Ben Dover"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1999 movie received the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 72nd Academy Awards ceremony in 2000?", "correct_answer": "American Beauty", "incorrect_answers": ["The Insider", "The Sixth Sense", "The Green Mile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the known top speed that a snow avalanche can reach?", "correct_answer": "60 mph (95 km/h)", "incorrect_answers": ["85 mph (135 km/h)", "45 mph (72 km/h)", "30 mph (48 km/h)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What frog is the most poisonous?", "correct_answer": "Dart Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Cane Toad", "Corroboree Frog", "Red-Eyed tree frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning movie directed by Martin Scorsese ends with the Biblical quote All I know is this: Once I was blind, and now I can see?", "correct_answer": "Raging Bull", "incorrect_answers": ["The Color of Money", "Cape Fear", "The Aviator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the term for a small, thin piece of skin, especially the skin that comes off the body after a sunburn?", "correct_answer": "blype", "incorrect_answers": ["bobo", "olea", "obol"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Crow, how many knives did Tin-Tin throw at Eric before being foiled by his own blade?", "correct_answer": "Three", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Four", "Two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who shouldnt live in Gotham according to fictional character Jack Napier?", "correct_answer": "decent people", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman", "honest people", "smart people"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rapper appeared in the opening scene of the 2000 action\u2013comedy Charlies Angels as Mr. Jones, an African priest who turns out to be Dylan in disguise?", "correct_answer": "LL Cool J", "incorrect_answers": ["P. Diddy", "Snoop Dogg", "Will Smith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which ancient Greek historian is considered the Father of History?", "correct_answer": "Herodotus", "incorrect_answers": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Demitrios"]}]